question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The ghosts in &quot;Pac-Man&quot; and &quot;Ms. Pac-Man&quot; have completely different behavior.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Geography",
     "question": "Alaska is the largest state in the United States.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                                       "question": "The 2011 movie &quot;The Adventures of Tintin&quot; was directed by Steven Spielberg.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Several characters in &quot;Super Mario 64&quot; blink their eyes, including Mario himself.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Geography",
     "question": "San Marino is the only country completely surrounded by another country.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Musicals &amp; Theatres",
     "question": "IMAX stands for Image Maximum.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In &quot;Mario Kart 64&quot;, Waluigi is a playable character.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                                      "question": "The music group Daft Punk got their name from a negative review they recieved.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Mythology",
     "question": "In Norse mythology, Thor once dressed as a woman.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
                                       "question": "The mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]